{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Boiler \u0026 Radiator Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40281/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40281,"taskName":"Boiler or Radiator Heating System - Repair or Service","taskDescription":"Repair or Service a Boiler or Radiator Heating System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Boiler \u0026 Radiator Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":28,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Boiler Maintenance Replacement Heating Broiler","textMessagingName":"Svc Boiler/Radiator","rolloverLongDesc":"Heating, Heat, natural, Propane, Oil, Electric, pilot","rolloverShortDesc":"Typically boiler is in basement \u0026 radiators are in each room.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Service a Boiler or Radiator Heating System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Boiler \u0026 Radiator Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Leak Repair \u0026 Costs","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Boiler or Radiator Heat Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Boiler or Radiator Heating System - Repair or Service","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Boiler or Radiator Heating Project","urlName":"Boiler-or-Radiator-Heating-System-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Boiler \u0026 Radiator Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Boiler,Maintenance,Replacement,Heating,Broiler,air,ac,furnaces,,furnace,floor,wall,electric,dehumidifying,conractor,cooling,centralair,airconditioning,central,btus,boilers,heaters,lamp,heat,baseboard,airwell,units,systems,condition,test,water,hot,vents,pump,ducts,controller,geothermal,gas,radiant,conditioning,HVAC,System,Radiator","emcCategoryOid":-12040,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":584,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40281/":{"taskOID":40281,"originalTaskOID":40281,"setID":584,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6995,"questionDisplayText":"Type of system","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of boiler system needs to be repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10316,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10317,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane gas fired ","answerDisplayText":"Propane gas fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10318,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil fired","answerDisplayText":"Oil fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10319,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electric fired","answerDisplayText":"Electric fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":993,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What describes the nature of the problem? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Power failure","answerDisplayText":"Power failure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4204,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No heat in one location","answerDisplayText":"No heat in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4203,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No heat in all locations","answerDisplayText":"No heat in all locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1698,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cracked radiator","answerDisplayText":"Cracked radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3517,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Leaky radiator","answerDisplayText":"Leaky radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3516,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Leaky boiler","answerDisplayText":"Leaky boiler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4686,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Pilot light out on boiler","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light out on boiler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1122,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Broken baseboard radiator cover","answerDisplayText":"Broken baseboard radiator cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4999,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Radiant heat pump not functioning","answerDisplayText":"Radiant heat pump not functioning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2912,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Hammering noise in radiator","answerDisplayText":"Hammering noise in radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6430,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Too much heat in some locations","answerDisplayText":"Too much heat in some locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10161,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6995,"questionDisplayText":"Type of system","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of boiler system needs to be repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10316,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10317,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane gas fired ","answerDisplayText":"Propane gas fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10318,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil fired","answerDisplayText":"Oil fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10319,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electric fired","answerDisplayText":"Electric fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10316,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural gas fired","answerDisplayText":"Natural gas fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10317,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Propane gas fired ","answerDisplayText":"Propane gas fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10318,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oil fired","answerDisplayText":"Oil fired","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10319,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electric fired","answerDisplayText":"Electric fired ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":993,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What describes the nature of the problem? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Power failure","answerDisplayText":"Power failure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4204,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No heat in one location","answerDisplayText":"No heat in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4203,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No heat in all locations","answerDisplayText":"No heat in all locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1698,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cracked radiator","answerDisplayText":"Cracked radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3517,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Leaky radiator","answerDisplayText":"Leaky radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3516,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Leaky boiler","answerDisplayText":"Leaky boiler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4686,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Pilot light out on boiler","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light out on boiler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1122,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Broken baseboard radiator cover","answerDisplayText":"Broken baseboard radiator cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4999,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Radiant heat pump not functioning","answerDisplayText":"Radiant heat pump not functioning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2912,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Hammering noise in radiator","answerDisplayText":"Hammering noise in radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6430,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Too much heat in some locations","answerDisplayText":"Too much heat in some locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10161,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2758,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gas smell","answerDisplayText":"Gas smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Power failure","answerDisplayText":"Power failure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4204,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No heat in one location","answerDisplayText":"No heat in one location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4203,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No heat in all locations","answerDisplayText":"No heat in all locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1698,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cracked radiator","answerDisplayText":"Cracked radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3517,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Leaky radiator","answerDisplayText":"Leaky radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3516,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Leaky boiler","answerDisplayText":"Leaky boiler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4686,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Pilot light out on boiler","answerDisplayText":"Pilot light out on boiler","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1122,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Broken baseboard radiator cover","answerDisplayText":"Broken baseboard radiator cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4999,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Radiant heat pump not functioning","answerDisplayText":"Radiant heat pump not functioning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2912,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Hammering noise in radiator","answerDisplayText":"Hammering noise in radiator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6430,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Too much heat in some locations","answerDisplayText":"Too much heat in some locations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10161,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Annual/Preventative Maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}